有很多原因你可能更好的将
There's a number of reasons you'd be potentially better
你的App分解为不同的活动。拥有一个
off breaking your app into different activities. Having a
完整的活动增加你代码的复杂度，
single monolithic activity increases the complexity of your code,
使得创建和管理意图过滤更为
making the creation and management of intent filters much
艰难，使其更难维护，测试，
harder and making it more difficult to maintain, test,
代码理解。这也增加了
and read your activity code. It also increases the
耦合的风险并使其
risk of tightly coupling independent components and makes it
更易于引入安全风险，如果
much more likely to introduce security risks if the
这一单一活动包含敏感信息和可共享的信息。
single activity includes both sensitive information and information that's safe
好的经验是创建一个
to share. A good rule of thumb is to create a
新的活动，在任何改变发生的时候。比如，显示
new activity whenever the context changes. For example, displaying a
不同种类的数据，在从查看到输入的过程中。
different kind of data, while switching from viewing to entering data.